The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Forty-Third Episode
The Spider Island
Sapphire Caught in a Trap
All right!
Hop, hop! Hup, hup!
I'm sorry. Help me!
I'm scared!
A ship! It's so pretty! Wonderful! Cool!
Oh, right! I'll go tell Sapphire!
Sapphire, wake up, wake up!
There's a lovely swan ship!
A swan ship?
Wow! What an amazing ship! Whose could it be?
Hey, hey, let's hurry and check it out!
I kind of want to step aboard.
Please, please, step right on board.
Grand Duke Duralumin had this ship custom-built specially for Lord Sapphire.
Come on, right this way, please.
Grand Duke Duralumin? That seems a bit suspicious.
Still, it is tempting...
Come on, right this way.
Well then, let me step aboard just for a moment and take a look inside.
My dearest, I've prepared a wonderful present for you!
Candy?
It's nothing so simple. Tomorrow, all of Silverland will be yours.
That beautiful swan ship was rigged from the very start.
The ship's destination is... the Rose...
Who's there?
Oh, it's you.
Everything is going smoothly.
Are you sure about that?
The ship has been rigged. Now we just sit back and watch.
Everything on the island is set, too.
On that deserted island, Sapphire will disappear without anyone knowing,
and the rest will go according to your plan.
Very well. Do it right..
What a beautiful swan ship.
That's amazing!
It's beautiful.
Traveling on a ship like this would be fun.
Going on and on forever.
This ship, it's moving on its own!
Hey! Help me!
Hey! Somebody!
What's that?
Hey! Help me!
Sapphire!
Marlin!
Franz!
Prince Franz!
I guess it was no use...
This rudder isn't working at all!
We've been swept all the way out to sea.
Franz is all the way over there!
Sapphire, I'm coming!
Here goes!
Franz!
Glad I made it in time. I was just out for a morning walk.
Wow, incredible!
Hey, why don't you come inside here?
Hmm? I'm fine right here.
Wow, amazing. This island is full of roses.
But it's strange.
With all these flowers blooming, there isn't even a hint of that lovely scent.
It's a strange island, but let's walk around a bit anyway.
A rose tunnel!
Oh no, wait up!
Where did Tink go?
Tink!
Tink! Tink! Tink! Where are you?
R-Roses...!
Sapphire! Look out! Something's wrong!
Franz!
What are these guys?
Quick, hide behind me! Are you all right?
I'm a man! Leave this to me!
Here I come, monster cats!
Franz! The cats!
Franz!
Sapphire!
Take that!
Over here, monster cats!
You're facing the Ribbon Knight!
Franz!
Where on earth could he have gone?
Tink!
Franz!
Sapphire!
Tink!
Thank goodness.
Tink, come on, pull yourself together.
Thank you.
Looks like Prince Franz was caught by the cats, too.
I knew it, this island is no ordinary place.
I'm sorry, it's my fault. I'll go search for Prince Franz!
But searching a terrifying island like this...?
Tink!
How strange.
This cobweb is as thick as a rope.
There must be something going on. Let's follow this thread.
So you're awake, Franz.
Who are you?! Why did you capture me?!
Me?
I am the guardian of this island, Spider Man.
My master ordered me to take Princess Sapphire from the swan ship
and wipe her out in total secrecy.
I never expected to get a bonus like you along with her.
I'll send you to heaven first!
So everything was a trap from the start?
Exactly.
Now, prepare to share the same fate as pretty Princess Sapphire. Farewell!
Franz
Who are you?
I came to save you.
It's no use—this isn't ordinary thread. Wait, Tink, go find some water.
Where's Sapphire?
You don't think... Sapphire escaped safely! Rest assured!
Thank goodness...
But Ribbon Knight, just who are you to Sapphire?
This is no time for that!
We have to get out of here while the Spider Man is asleep!
It's just water, what do we do with it?
Hurry, splash it!
Hurry, let's run!
They ran off!
I'm exhausted!
Tink! Hurry, or they'll find us!
Go on ahead! I can't go any further!
Come on!
A mere scratch from this sword is fatal. Take this!
That goes for you over there, too!
Franz! Hang in there!
Are you all right?
We have to get out of this forest fast!
Stay strong!
Just you wait!
Tink,
they say a cure grows wherever a venomous monster makes its nest.
Look around here and find that herb for me.
Understood. Right away...
Sapphire...
Yes!
Damn it.
Sapphire...
He's having a nightmare.
Poor thing...
Hang in there, Franz!
Sapphire!
I'm right here. Rest easy.
Thank you, Sapphire.
I found it, I found it! Apply this, and the Spider Man's venom will...
Huh? Now you're dressed as Sapphire...
Quick, the herbs!
Right!
Will he be okay?
He'll be fine now.
Silence! I'll tolerate no excuses!
True, I didn't tell you to kill Franz as well.
But you're an assassin! How could you lose to a kid like that?!
I haven't lost yet.
The moment he stabbed me, I wounded him with my dagger.
By now, the poison has spread through his body. He can't possibly be alive.
I came here to claim Princess Sapphire's body.
A promise is a promise.
Is the Spider Man such a coward to stay in bed over a mere scratch?
Now, use your prized thread to get rid of Sapphire!
If they're injured too, they couldn't have escaped the island yet.
Now, go!
Sapphire?
Yeah. She nursed me all night long.
Tink already put Sapphire on the swan ship and sent her back to the castle.
But...
You must've been having a fever dream.
Come on, we need to go fix the boat.
You get some rest for now.
That should take care of the chores, right?
I'm all better now, too. We can finally go home.
Not so fast! Princess Sapphire, I'll be taking your life!
Spider Man?!
You're wearing a ridiculous disguise, but you're Princess Sapphire, aren't you!
I'm the Knight of the Ribbon.
Doesn't matter. You won't leave this island alive.
Get the little one!
Let's go!
That face doesn't scare me!
Look, I brought some catnip.
This is the end!
Tink, are you all right?
Yeah.
They all ate the catnip and calmed right down.
Damn, foiled again!
The Ribbon Knight, Tink, and Franz... They're formidable foes.
But I am Duralumin! I won't back down like this. Next time, for sure!
Sapphire, even if they say it was just a fever dream,
I will never forget the happiness of that moment when you nursed me back to health.
Franz,
thank you.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if demons come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP